The best medical care minimum wage can buy.
Code 3 is a comedy, action film directed by Christopher Leone.
A burned-out paramedic tries to survive his last 24 hours
on the job while training a new recruit.
Randy, played by Rainn Wilson.
Mike, played by Lil Rel Howery.
Jessica, played by Aimee Carrero.
Shanice, played by Yvette Nicole Brown.
Dr. Serano, played by Rob Riggle.
Officer Taggert, played by Page Kennedy.
Code 3 is a 2025 American comedy drama film written by Christopher Leone and Patrick Pianezza,
directed by Leone and starring Rainn Wilson, Lil Rel Howery and Aimee Carrero.
The film explores themes of satire, tragicomedy,
admiring, appreciative, objective.
The tone is lighthearted.